Seino! This is Angelem!
Today, I'm going to meet Yukiho Shimobata and Hana Goto, who joined Angulum a few days ago, and the other members for the first time!
Yay!
Oh my gosh!
Everyone already knows that the two of you are going to join us,
But today is the first time for us to meet,
Rin Kawada is not feeling well and has not been able to return yet,
So, today, we will have this member and Kero again,
So, here they are today, the two of them!
Wow!
I'm so excited.
It's my first time as a junior,
But I'm like, "Oh, no, not yet, not yet!
No, no, not yet!
I'm a little confused,
I'm still a little flustered, so I'm sure I'll feel it when I meet him.
I'm really looking forward to it!
Kawada-chan, this is the first time that someone younger than you has joined the group,
For the past two years, you were the youngest,
I'm not the youngest for two years, so I'm not sure if I'm going to be the youngest,
Well, I will continue to do my best.
I guess we are both pretty big.
I'm so happy!
Well, I'll show you the two of them now!
So, where are they coming from?
From where?
You'd better look for them.
Who? Don't look for it.
It's better to hide it.
Point to where you think it might be.
Se-no!
Now, let's see it from that side.
Okay?
Are you in the middle?
Back of the camera.
You're all right. Face forward, please.
Okay, I'm going to ask you two to come in.
Come on in!
Whoa!
Open the door properly!
The door has opened properly.
Please introduce yourselves again.
I am 16 years old, a high school sophomore from Okayama, Japan.
My hobby is sign language, which I am currently studying.
I will try to do the self-introduction I just said in sign language.
Here is the camera there.
I am 16 years old, a high school sophomore, from Okayama Prefecture.
I am Kanon Yuki.
Wow!
That's great!
You have a wonderful hobby.
Yes, I do. I am 14 years old, a junior high school student from Saitama, Japan.
I like ham.
Cute.
Here are the introductions.
I've actually met both of you. What do you think?
Cute.
They're cute.
So am I.
They are taller than the contestants.
Is that so?
How tall are you?
Both of us. 161 centimeters.
And Momo Takano?
I measured her the other day and she was 156.7cm,
She's probably a little closer to 157cm.
Oh, wow.
I'm a 157cm girl.
Momo-chan is 48.5 cm.
Is there anything you would like to ask me?
I guess I'd like to ask about my idols first.
Angstrom? Or Halo Pro?
I'm a member of Halo Pro.
Then both.
You're greedy.
I'm greedy.
It's really okay.
Suddenly I'm fine.
I've been told that I'm going to be a member of Angels from today,
I'm really okay even if I'm talking to someone completely different.
I'm really okay.
I really love you all,
I really love you all, but I'm Rika Shimakura for Halo Project as a whole, and Rika Sasaki for Angstrom,
I'm Rika Shimakura for Halo Project as a whole, and Rika Sasaki for Angstrom.
Thank you.
I'm so happy. You are so cute.
I'm a former member of Morning Musume。 Sayumi Michishige from Morning Musume,
I respect Sayumi Michishige from former Morning Musume and Tamura from Juice-Juice in Halo Project,
I love all the members of Angulum,
I love them all.
Thank you.
I love you from God.
Feels good?
You guys are good friends to begin with, right?
Yes, we are.
That's what the trainee manager said,
Because we are all good friends.He said we're all good friends.
Yeah?
Do you understand that?
Do you understand?
It's a spirit of mutual respect.
Well, then, if you're in that group, you go first.
Okay.
Yes, I'll go first.
I think we had a term of endearment when I was a trainee,
I'm not sure if it's going to change again,
Do you have a preference for what you would like to be called?
Certainly.
Okay, cute.
I was called Yuta,
Yuta.
I wanted him to make something,
Here we go.
Too much change.
I want to change again.
Some people change after all even if they make it.
Certainly.
The current phase.
In the first stage.
Which is better.
Sure, I'm sure.
You can totally take it this way too.
I see.
Yuki is cute, right?
She's cute.
I wish I could go to Yuki.
You're cute.
You want to go, don't you?
She's cute, isn't she?
It's still cute.
But you want a little bit more, don't you?
Favorite food, animals, etc.?
Sure.
It's Keron.
Keron.
His food is corn,
And his animal is a rabbit.
I see.
Let's go.
Go, go, go, go!
Gobyapin is cute.
But it's a go-pyong.
Because he's a go-between.
But, she's totally with Seira-chan.
I'll give up going.
Hurry up!
I'll yield to you on the way.
I'll yield.
Because you're so cute.
Because he's cute.
I'll yield.
There it is. There it is.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll go.
Is it okay if everyone calls you "go-pyon"?
Yes, I'm fine.
Harada-chan, please be my go-between.
Do you have any, Harada-chan?
I said, "I have flowers over here,
Me, too,
Can I have them attached?
I'd like you to put them on, wouldn't you?
I've gone to a lot of trouble to get them for Aika Azumi and her seniors, right?
Yes.
Harada-chan is so cute.
Until now, Gozuka was too simple,
I didn't get many people to wear them,
I see. You can say "Gozou-chan" and "Hana-chan".
You can say "Gozashira-chan" and "Hana-chan", can't you?
That's true.
I want to make this one a little better.
I'd like to make something out of it.
What do you have? Favorite food.
I heard.
I heard you once.
Do you have any animals?
I like cats.
A cat.
Or Hana-nyan.
But there's a Nyan?
Really?
Nyan.
I raised my hand.
Hana-nyan is cute, but...
I'm sorry. It's okay if you're seriously worried,
Can I ask you to speak?
My senpai has a physical complaint.
Hanana's super cute.
Hanana's so cute.
Hanana's leeks.
There are a lot of leeks that have "u" in them.
I don't know.
But..,
So, ah no, no.So, ah no.
Hanana.
Then, let's go.
She's cute.
You haven't done that since Matsuura-san.
Then, let's do it. Hanana?
Yes.
It's cute.
I like it.
YUUPPYON and HANANA.
It's cute.
Then, let's make it YUTPYON and HANANA.
From now on, we'll be working as Angstrom,
I'm also okay with voice acting from now on,
I'm sure they'll call us a lot,
Please call them YUCCPYON and HANANA.
Please do so.
And now, I have a sudden announcement,
I have an announcement for you two.
First of all, the members here...
Oh, my God.
It's tough.
It's great.
Can I ask you to open up the middle for a second?
Don't go that way.
Help Rin.
Yukiho,
This is actually a door,
Right and left inside?
May I ask Yukiho to come in here?
Yes.
Rinrin didn't do it.
Rin Rin, I'm changing now.
Rin Rin, please leave now.
I'm so disappointed.
It's going to be a door.
If you open the door, it will open.
This is the first job for Julm. This is it.
Yay!
Two members will be here.
Se-no!
★Yay!
So, Yukiho-chan is hot pink,
Yukiho became a hot pink and Kana became a sea blue.
Congratulations!
They are so cute.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Cute.
So cute.
All I can hear is screams.
So, Yukiho is hot pink,
And Kana-chan will be sea blue.
Thank you very much.
What do you think?
It's my favorite color, so I'm happy.
Really?
I've always wanted to wear blue and find my own,
I'm so happy and happy.
I'm so happy.
This is the only color I could find for the wind boat right now,
Yukiho-chan's is a darker pink,
Yukiho's is a darker pink, like Momona's. Sea Blue is a little lighter than mine.
Sea Blue will be a little lighter than me. I think Sea Blue will be a little lighter than me.
I heard it won't go to light blue,
So, the two of us are now hot pink and sea blue.
Thank you very much.
I hope you will wave them a lot at live concerts.
We hope you will wave it a lot at live performances,
I think you two will be doing more and more performances from now on,
I hope you will continue to support the new Angelem as well.
That's all for now!
I hope to see you all again soon!
Everyone is so kind and cheerful,
I am so glad that there are no more members of Angulum,
I was really happy that there are no more Angelem members here.
I was really happy to see them,
I was really happy when I was there,
I was thinking, "Why all? I couldn't even think of how to organize it,
I couldn't even tell you how it was organized,
But now I think I'm going to be No. 1,
I am super happy.
The color of the members is hot pink,
I have been saying that I like hot pink since I was a member of Kenshu Sensei,
I am very happy.
I want to wear a lot of hot pink from now on.
It's so cute and there are so many angels,
I wondered if I was really one of them,
I wondered if I was really one of them, but I am so happy that they chose me,
I am really happy.
I'm still confused about whether it's a dream or reality,
I'm still confused about whether it's a dream or reality, but now I know it's more real than it was then.
I really like the color blue,
I thought it would be nice if it was blue,
So I am very, very happy.I am so insanely happy.
I think blue is a color that people with high fighting skills wear,
So I would like to improve my skills and do my best,
I would like to improve my skills and do my best,
It's a bit like Takeuchi's blue,
I also want to become a wonderful person like you.
I am very happy to hear that.
I really wanted to have it on me,
I am really happy.
I'm Yupyon.
My name is Hanana.
I will do my best as an ajuru from now on, so please support me.
Bye bye!
You're so cute.
Thank you very much.
It's my last time. Have fun.
Okay.
There are only two shows left.
I look forward to working with you.
Let's do our best.
Yes, I will.
Let's do our best, Yukirinu.
Yay!
Anyway.
This hand-over is over for today.
Yes, let's have fun. Let's have fun.
Yes, I'll be there.
Okay, this is Meira, Kinoshita, Shiyou, Akane, Taira, Yupyong, Hanane, and Kinoshita from the paper corner.
Keep Ya Drama.
It was keep-ya-drama.
Okay, see you guys.
Yes, I'll see you all.
See you again.
Okay.
I'm off.
First time. It was fun.
It's filled with the goodness of Angstrom.
It's like I can tell how good they are just by looking at them.
Thank you very much.
It's hard to put into words how excited and nervous I am,
But I am very excited.
I am more excited than nervous right now,
I'm sure I'll be really nervous even in the corners of the show,
I hope we will be able to go out together in high spirits and happiness.
This will be the first time for the two of us to perform together as Angstrom.
Yes, I will do my best. We will do our best.
We only have to introduce ourselves at the unveiling,
I'll do my best to make the audience smile.
I'll do my best.
Hi!
I'm off!
Last check.
You look cute today.
Yes, this is Tomo.
I'm off!
Bye bye!
As I announced the other day,
A new member will join our group.
So let's have them come out right away. Please welcome our new member!
Congratulations!
Let me introduce myself.
I'm going to join Angulum.
I'm from Okayama Prefecture.
Okay. From Okayama Prefecture.
Born in Okayama Prefecture. I am 16 years old and a sophomore in high school.
My member color is hot pink.
Beautiful.
I'm going to join Angelem as well.
Born in Saitama Prefecture. A junior in high school. 15 years old, this is Hana Goto.
Member color is,
Member color is ,
I am a new member.
Congratulations!
We look forward to working with you.
I'm happy for you.
He's cute.
Wait, isn't it too cute? This dress.
It's cute.
It's cute. Are you happy?
Yeah, I'm happy.
I hope everyone is looking forward to it.
So, thank you two new penumbers.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
This is sweat, so don't worry about it.
Thank you very much.
I got very goofy.
I was so happy to see the beautiful hot pink!
I'm very happy to have fun and to feel that I've really become a member of Angstrom.
Thank you very much.
Um, wait a minute.
Wait a minute, please.
I think that during my time as a trainee, I worked hard to see this format,
I want to continue to do my best as a member of Angelem.
I think the word "happiness" is the best word for me right now.
It was beautiful.It was beautiful.
Hot pink my favorite color, and everyone immediately brought it back to the hot pink color,
That made me so happy, I cried.
Hana-chan said earlier that she was happy, and it was a happy day.
First of all, when the member colors were announced, it was instantaneous,
The penlights around us were seam red,
I felt happy.
As a member of Angelem, I will continue to shine as Angelem from now on,
I will continue to shine as the strongest idol, so please support me.
As a member of Angelem, I still lack a lot of skills in singing and dancing,
I would like to work hard so that I can give a wonderful performance like my seniors,
I also want to work hard to become the ideal person that I want to be.
I would like to ask for your support from now on.
Okay, ready.
Okay, okay.
Thank you very much.